CHINONSO JOHN NKPOLUKWU

Web Developer Professional

Address: 3012/220 Spencer Street, Melbourne, VIC 3000

Phone: 0401823031

Email: john.nkp1@gmail.com

Portfolio: johnnsonkp GitHub: https://github.com/johnnsonkp. Linkedin: chinonso-john-nkpolukwu

Software developer student and professional, with over 7 years of experience in customer service environments, seeking the successful application of software developer knowledge and customer service and IT experience into a Front-end Developer role.

SKILLS

Front-End	Back End	Source Control	FrameWorks	UI/UX
Javascript ES6 / jQuery	REST / MySQL	Git(Git Flow)	Bootstrap	Wire-framing
CSS / SASS/ SCSS	MongoDB	SCRUM / Agile	Ruby on Rails	Prototyping
HTML	Heroku	Github		Adobe XD

PROJECTS

CozyTees: Live Site

HTML | CSS/SCSS | Javascript | Ruby on Rails

→ A two sided marketplace application with stripe payment integration

Bitflix: Live Site

HTML | CSS/SCSS | Javascript | Ruby on Rails

→ Movie database application on rails created with the fetch API.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Entry Officer, {REMOTE}
My Emergency Dr, Sydney - [2019 - Present]

- →Exceptional data entry for industry leader in tele-health
- → Providing administrative support to emergency medicine specialists and management team
- →Liaising with other allied health care professionals remotely

Member Care Consultant HCF Insurance, Parramatta - [2018 - 2019]

- →In depth understanding of the Australian healthcare system, and the ability to relay information to members.
- →Expert troubleshooting when handling members online gueries.
- → Selling life insurance by educating members in order to meet daily and monthly KPIs.

Customer Service Representative, Inbound & Outbound Specialist NRMA Motoring & Services, Sydney Olympic Park - [2016 - 2018]

- →Expert customer servicing, whilst identifying new sales, up-selling and cross-selling opportunities.
- → Cross-skilled in multitude areas including insurance, roadside assistance, inbound and outbound.
- →Fluency navigating range of business systems.

EDUCATION

- → Coder Academy / Full stack web developer bootcamp
- → RMIT / Bachelor of Information Technology

